Jiang Nan.
جيانغ نان.
If.
إذا.
If I... Forget
إذا كنت ... انسى
it,
هو - هي،
What are you trying to say?
ماذا تحاول ان تقول؟
Are you really okay?
هل انت حقا بخير
It's okay. Don't you know
حسنا.  لا تعرف
that
الذي - التي
half of the conversation is very appetizing?
نصف المحادثة فاتح للشهية جدا؟
Nannan,
متأصل،
my sister-in-law is missing,
أخت زوجي مفقودة ،
Help me look for it.
ساعدني في البحث عنه
Caiyun, Caiyun,
كايون ، كايون ،
sister-in-law,
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة،
Caiyun,
كايون ،
Auntie,
العمة
Excuse me,
اعذرني،
did you see a cardigan in gray,
هل رأيت سترة صوفية باللون الرمادي ،
The woman with hair here,
المرأة ذات الشعر هنا ،
no
رقم
I don't think I saw Caiyun
لا أعتقد أنني رأيت Caiyun
Thank you, sister-in-law,
شكرا لك يا أخت الزوج ،
Caiyun,
كايون ،
Aunt,
عمة،
Did my mom say anything to you before she left?
هل قالت لك أمي أي شيء قبل أن تغادر؟
Nothing?
لا شئ؟
As soon as I turned around, Mrs. Gong disappeared.
بمجرد أن استدرت ، اختفت السيدة غونغ.
Jiang Nan,
جيانغ نان ،
go to the place where Auntie often goes. Auntie
اذهب إلى المكان الذي تذهب إليه العمة غالبًا.  العمة
and I will look for it along the street nearby.
وسأبحث عنه على طول الشارع القريب.
Chengcheng,
تشنغتشنغ ،
you don't know the way.
لا تعرف الطريق.
Be careful.
كن حذرا.
Okay,
تمام،
Caiyun,
كايون ،
Sister-in-law,
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة،
Caiyun.
كايون.
Sister-in-law.
أخت الزوج أو اخت الزوجة.
Have you seen my husband?
هل رأيت زوجي؟
I … My husband is about this
أنا ... زوجي عن هذا
tall, wearing a tool,
طويل القامة يرتدي أداة
No.
رقم.
What a good dog.
يا له من كلب جيد.
Caiyun.
كايون.
Chengcheng,
تشنغتشنغ ،
I want to see a movie.
اريد مشاهدة فيلم.
The movies Jiang Hai used to
الأفلام التي اعتاد جيانغ هاي على ذلك
take me to,
خذني ل،
Old cinema,
السينما القديمة
Caiyun.
كايون.
According to the patient's description,
حسب وصف المريض:
she used to be in her hometown,
اعتادت أن تكون في مسقط رأسها ،
Living and dating with her husband.
العيش والتعارف مع زوجها.
I remember it very clearly,
أتذكرها بوضوح شديد ،
the cinema.
السينما.
I want to ask,
اريد أن أسأل،
where is this place?
اين يوجد ذلك المكان؟
Lide Road,
شارع لايد ،
Shouldn't there be
لا ينبغي أن يكون هناك
a Red Star Cinema on Lide Road?
سينما ريد ستار في لايد رود؟
Why is the cinema missing?
لماذا السينما مفقودة؟
Red Star Cinema,
سينما ريد ستار ،
it was torn down years ago.
تم هدمه منذ سنوات.
Tear it down.
هدمه.
The cinema
السينما
is torn down.
تم هدمه.
It's that woman.
إنها تلك المرأة.
Mom,
أم،
It's all our fault.
كل هذا خطأنا.
It's all because of us that Shu Qian died.
كل شيء بسببنا مات شو تشيان.
It's because she can't get over it,
لأنها لا تستطيع تجاوز الأمر ،
don't think so.
لا أعتقد ذلك.
No,
رقم،
I really didn't expect
أنا حقا لم أتوقع
things to turn out like this.
أشياء لتتحول مثل هذا.
I'm going to kill you!
سأقتلك!
I'll kill you.
سأقتلك.
Caiyun,
كايون ،
are you okay?
انت بخير؟
Many oranges,
العديد من البرتقال ،
are you dying for this woman?
هل تموت من أجل هذه المرأة؟
Zhan Zhilin, what were you doing just now?
Zhan Zhilin ، ماذا كنت تفعل الآن؟
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Why did you take Chengcheng away? Go away.
لماذا أخذت Chengcheng بعيدا؟  يبتعد.
Let go of me!
ترك لي!
Where are you taking me?
إلى أين تأخذني؟
If you don't want them to know about your illness,
إذا كنت لا تريدهم أن يعرفوا عن مرضك ،
just come with me.
فقط تعال معي.
Get in the car.
اركب السيارة.
Zhan Zhilin.
زان تشيلين.
Jiang Nan.
جيانغ نان.
-Caiyun. -Caiyun, it's
-كيون. -كيون ، إنه
me. -It's my sister-in-law. I'm
أنا.  -إنها أخت زوجي.  انا
Jiang
جيانغ
Hai.
اثنين.
I'm Jiang Hai,
أنا جيانغ هاي ،
Caiyun,
كايون ،
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Jiang Hai,
جيانغ هاي ،
Auntie,
العمة
take my mom home first.
خذ أمي إلى المنزل أولاً.
I'll get Chengcheng back.
سأعيد Chengcheng.
Okay,
تمام،
Your mom has me.
أمك معي.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Drive safely.
قد بأمان.
Got it.
فهمتك.
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Why did you take it out on me for what happened between you and Jiang Nan?
لماذا انتقدتني بسبب ما حدث بينك وبين جيانغ نان؟
She's just a patient.
إنها مجرد مريضة.
She's innocent.
إنها بريئة.
Stop the car.
أوقف السيارة.
Where are you taking me?
إلى أين تأخذني؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I want to save your life.
أريد أن أنقذ حياتك.
I can't stand by and watch you die.
لا أستطيع الوقوف ومشاهدتك تموت.
I know
أنا أعرف
what's wrong with me.
ما خطبتي.
It's not your turn to interfere with me.
ليس دورك للتدخل معي.
Stop the car!
أوقف السيارة!
Are you crazy?
هل أنت مجنون؟
Come on,
هيا،
Stop fighting! Stop fighting!
وقف القتال!  وقف القتال!
How did you become like this?
كيف صرت هكذا؟
It's all because he worships you.
كل هذا لأنه يعبدك.
And from your crazy mother.
ومن والدتك المجنونة.
Say it again.
قلها ثانية.
Jiang Nan.
جيانغ نان.
If it happens again,
إذا حدث ذلك مرة أخرى ،
I won't let you go.
لن أدعك تذهب.
Don't move.
.لا تتحرك
It's okay.
حسنا.
This small injury is nothing.
هذه الإصابة الصغيرة لا شيء.
I'll be fine in a couple of days.
سأكون بخير في غضون يومين.
You're bleeding and you said you were fine.
أنت تنزف وقلت أنك بخير.
You were scared today too.
كنت خائفا اليوم أيضا.
Go to bed early.
اذهب الى السرير مبكرا.
You don't have to
لا داعي لذلك
worry about my mom.
تقلق بشأن أمي.
My aunt will stay with her.
ستبقى عمتي معها.
Why do you think Zhan Zhilin
لماذا تعتقد Zhan Zhilin
is so mean to me?
هل يعني ذلك بالنسبة لي؟
What happened between you two?
ماذا حدث بينكما؟
Don't ask.
لا تسأل.
And why Zhan Zhilin said
ولماذا قال Zhan Zhilin
it was all thanks to Auntie.
كان كل ذلك بفضل العمة.
I told you not to ask.
قلت لك لا تسأل.
Sorry,
آسف،
I'm in a bad mood.
أنا في مزاج سيء.
Go to bed early.
اذهب الى السرير مبكرا.
Why are you still up?
لماذا مازلت مستيقظا؟
But
ولكن
it doesn't matter,
لا يهم،
Sooner or later,
عاجلا أم آجلا،
all of you,
كلكم،
will leave me.
سوف يتركني.
I really want to go back to the past,
أريد حقًا أن أعود إلى الماضي ،
at that time,
فى ذلك التوقيت،
My dad is still here.
والدي لا يزال هنا.
Zhan Zhilin and I can
أنا وزان Zhilin
play music without any worries,
تشغيل الموسيقى دون أي قلق ،
I can't go back.
لا أستطيع العودة.
It's gone.
لقد ذهب.
There's nothing left.
لم يتبق هناك شيء.
Jiang Nan, stop drinking.
جيانغ نان ، توقف عن الشرب.
Stop drinking.
توقف عن الشرب.
Many oranges.
كثير من البرتقال.
Please don't
من فضلك لا
leave me.
أتركني.
Please
لو سمحت
stay by my side all the time.
ابق بجانبي طوال الوقت.
Okay?
تمام؟
What did you do last night?
ماذا فعلت الليلة الماضية؟
Many oranges. Many oranges.
كثير من البرتقال.  كثير من البرتقال.
You didn't drink.
أنت لم تشرب.
Why are you so confused?
لماذا انت مرتبك جدا؟
Sorry
آسف
to wake you up.
لإيقاظك.
I lost my earring.
لقد فقدت حلقى.
I'm looking for earrings.
أنا أبحث عن أقراط.
You lost your earring.
لقد فقدت قرطك.
Let me find it for you.
دعني أجدها لك.
Last night,
ليلة أمس،
right?
الصحيح؟
What?
ماذا؟
No.
رقم.
I haven't said what it is yet?
أنا لم أقل ما هو عليه حتى الآن؟
You don't have anything?
ليس لديك شئ
You,
أنت،
You didn't rinse
أنت لم تشطف
your mouth. Your alcohol is
فمك.  كحولك هو
too strong.
قوي جدا.
Did nothing really happen
لم يحدث شيء حقا
between us last night?
بيننا الليلة الماضية؟
By the way,
على فكرة،
clean it up later.
تنظيفه لاحقًا.
I'll go back first.
سأعود أولا.
Why are you going back so soon?
لماذا ستعود قريبا جدا؟
Zhan Zhilin was able to find this place yesterday.
تمكنت Zhan Zhilin من العثور على هذا المكان أمس.
I'm sure the media can do the same.
أنا متأكد من أن وسائل الإعلام يمكن أن تفعل الشيء نفسه.
If I stay here,
إذا بقيت هنا ،
it'll disturb my mom's peace.
سوف يزعج سلام أمي.
After we leave,
بعد مغادرتنا ،
Auntie will move my mom to her house.
ستنقل العمة أمي إلى منزلها.
So that they won't be found out.
حتى لا يتم اكتشافهم.
Okay.
تمام.
Where is it?
أين هي؟
Nang,
متى،
Come on.
هيا.
Your mom is fine.
والدتك بخير.
You recognized me just now.
لقد عرفتني الآن.
I'll take care of her.
سأعتني بها.
In the meantime,
في هذه الأثناء،
please take care of my mom.
من فضلك اعتني بأمي.
Call me if you have any questions.
اتصل بي إذا كان لديك أي أسئلة.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Be careful on your way.
كن حذرا في طريقك.
We'll get going then.
سنبدأ بعد ذلك.
Get some sleep.
خذ قسطا من النوم.
I'll call you when we get there.
سأتصل بك عندما نصل إلى هناك.
No, thanks.
لا شكرا.
I'm not sleepy.
أنا لست نعسان.
By the way, Chengcheng,
بالمناسبة ، Chengcheng ،
I suddenly remembered something,
فجأة تذكرت شيئًا ،
Let's go and buy Doudou a birthday present.
دعنا نذهب ونشتري دودو هدية عيد ميلاد.
How do you know Doudou's birthday?
كيف تعرف عيد ميلاد دودو؟
Doudou's birthday.
عيد ميلاد دودو.
But you invited me
لكنك دعوتني
so many times.
مرات عديدة.
How should I choose?
كيف أختار؟
Kids nowadays are so happy.
الأطفال في الوقت الحاضر سعداء للغاية.
So many toys
الكثير من الألعاب
are too picky.
صعب الإرضاء للغاية.
Why don't we buy more?
لماذا لا نشتري المزيد؟
I don't have to be bored in the hospital
لا يجب أن أشعر بالملل في المستشفى
to cover up my current condition,
للتغطية على حالتي الحالية ،
He can't even play with these complicated toys.
لا يمكنه حتى اللعب بهذه الألعاب المعقدة.
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
gradual freezing is such a torturous disease.
التجميد التدريجي هو مثل هذا المرض المعذب.
The later the stage, the more you need the support of your family.
كلما تأخرت المرحلة ، كلما احتجت إلى دعم أسرتك.
I really don't know
أنا حقا لا أعرف
how Doudou's mom survived?
كيف نجت والدة دودو؟
Hello,
مرحبًا،
how old are you showing toys to?
كم عمرك تظهر الألعاب ل؟
Eight years old.
ثمانية سنوات.
We are
نحن
so young parents.
حتى الآباء الصغار.
Let's make our own choice.
دعونا نتخذ خيارنا بأنفسنا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
It's okay,
حسنا،
Chengcheng
تشنغتشنغ
Did Doudou mention it to you?
هل ذكرها دودو لك؟
Is there anything he really wants?
هل هناك أي شيء يريده حقًا؟
These puppies that I really want
هذه الجراء التي أريدها حقًا
are so cute.
لطيف جدا.
It has sprouted
لقد نبت
a lot of oranges,
الكثير من البرتقال ،
Restrain yourself.
كبح جماح نفسك.
We're here to pick a gift for Doudou.
نحن هنا لاختيار هدية لـ Doudou.
Then.
ثم.
Let's buy this Shiba Inu.
لنشتري هذا Shiba Inu.
He has a very good personality.
لديه شخصية جيدة جدا.
Although Shiba Inu is small now,
على الرغم من صغر حجم شبعا إينو الآن ،
When it grows up,
عندما يكبر ،
it will be naughty.
سيكون شقي.
It's not suitable for pockets.
انها ليست مناسبة للجيوب.
Then buy Schnauzer.
ثم شراء Schnauzer.
When Schnauzer grows up,
عندما يكبر Schnauzer ،
his eyelashes are super long,
رموشه طويلة جدًا ،
It's very cute,
لطيفة جدا،
but Schnauzer's words are too delicate.
لكن كلمات شنوزر حساسة للغاية.
Doudou's family couldn't take care of Doudou.
لم تستطع عائلة دودو الاعتناء بدودو.
How can I take care of it?
كيف يمكنني الاعتناء به؟
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
Let's buy Bomei,
لنشتري Bomei ،
Look at Bomei,
انظر إلى بومي ،
she doesn't eat much either,
هي أيضا لا تأكل كثيرا ،
It doesn't shed hair,
لا يتساقط الشعر ،
and it's cute and clingy.
وهو لطيف ولطيف.
It's perfect for Doudou.
إنه مثالي لـ Doudou.
That's it.
هذا هو.
Okay.
تمام.
Hey,
يا،
I found something.
لقد وجدت شيئا ما.
What did I find out?
ماذا اكتشفت؟
Gu Jiayi revealed the address of the nursing home that day.
كشف غو جياي عن عنوان دار المسنين في ذلك اليوم.
It's really her.
انها حقا هي.
Don't rush
لا تتسرع
out. What happened?
خارج.  ماذا حدث؟
Something came up,
حدث شيء ما ،
so you should leave now.
لذلك يجب أن تغادر الآن.
It's okay.
حسنا.
I'll walk you up first.
سوف أمشي معك أولاً.
Come on,
هيا،
Go back to your work.
عد إلى عملك.
I'll take care of
سأعتني به
Chengcheng,
تشنغتشنغ ،
Take care of the dog at home,
اعتني بالكلب في المنزل ،
and wait for me to come back.
وانتظر حتى أعود.
Why are you blushing?
لماذا تحمر خجلا؟
How am I blushing?
كيف أحمر خجلاً؟
It's too hot.
انها حارة جدا.
I'm here to be an assistant.
أنا هنا لأكون مساعدا.
I'm not here
انا لست هنا
to be a nanny,
لتكون مربية ،
Coke chicken wings,
أجنحة دجاج كوكاكولا ،
the same as last time.
نفس المرة الماضية.
I'm going to keep you from getting up and down on the treadmill.
سأمنعك من الصعود والنزول على جهاز المشي.
A lot of oranges.
الكثير من البرتقال.
What's this smell?
ما هذه الرائحة؟
Where's my moxa fever?
أين حمى موكسا؟
It promotes blood circulation,
يعزز الدورة الدموية ،
warms the body and the palace.
يدفئ الجسد والقصر.
Just because you're handsome,
فقط لأنك وسيم
you're disturbing the people. Do you know
أنت تزعج الناس.  هل تعرف
that playing games in your own house,
أن تلعب في منزلك ،
I didn't sing K
أنا لم أغني K.
again.
تكرارا.
Who am I disturbing? I've been here all morning,
من أنا مزعج؟  كنت هنا طوال الصباح ،
With so many words,
مع الكثير من الكلمات ،
are you going to let me rest?
هل ستدعني أرتاح؟
I'm not singing K at home.
أنا لا أغني K في المنزل.
Who are you disturbing?
من أنت مزعج؟
Are you satisfied?
هل أنت راض؟
I wrote a new song.
لقد كتبت أغنية جديدة.
Do you want to hear it?
هل تريد أن تسمعه؟
Please don't
من فضلك لا
leave me.
أتركني.
Jiang Nan,
جيانغ نان ،
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
I broke my promise.
لقد حنثت بوعدي.
I can't be with you anymore.
لا أستطيع أن أكون معك بعد الآن.
My existence
وجودي
will only make your life more troublesome.
ستجعل حياتك أكثر إزعاجًا.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Brother Nan,
الأخ نان ،
Nan,
في،
did you tell us
هل اخبرتنا
the address of Gu Jiayi Sanatorium?
عنوان مصحة جو جياي؟
Sanatorium,
مصحة،
is something wrong?
هل هناك خطأ؟
Auntie, are you okay?
العمة ، هل أنت بخير؟
You don't have to work so hard
ليس عليك العمل بجد
now that you're better than acting.
الآن بعد أن أصبحت أفضل من التمثيل.
Are you suspecting me?
هل تشك بي؟
Why don't you suspect a lot of oranges?
لماذا لا تشك في الكثير من البرتقال؟
She's the one
هي المختارة
who goes to the nursing home every day,
من يذهب إلى دار رعاية المسنين كل يوم ،
Many oranges can't be.
لا يمكن أن يكون العديد من البرتقال.
She can't be.
لا يمكنها أن تكون.
I did all the bad things.
لقد فعلت كل الأشياء السيئة.
Every time something goes wrong,
في كل مرة يحدث خطأ ما ،
why do you always suspect me in the first place,
لماذا تشك بي دائمًا في المقام الأول ،
I don't care if it has anything to do with you.
لا يهمني إذا كان الأمر يتعلق بك.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
don't bother my mom again.
لا تزعج أمي مرة أخرى.
She's a patient.
إنها مريضة.
He needs quiet treatment.
يحتاج إلى علاج هادئ.
Also,
ايضا،
no matter what means you use,
بغض النظر عن الوسائل التي تستخدمها ،
Many oranges and I
كثير من البرتقال وأنا
can't be separated.
لا يمكن فصلها.
Nan.
في.
The puppy is fed
يتم إطعام الجرو
50 grams of dry food twice a day,
50 جرام من الطعام الجاف مرتين في اليوم ،
Take a walk sooner or later.
تمشى عاجلاً أم آجلاً.
I was afraid that you would leave quietly.
كنت أخشى أن تغادر بهدوء.
I even bought a puppy.
حتى أنني اشتريت جروًا.
I want to find a reason to keep you.
أريد أن أجد سببًا لإبقائك.
But you left anyway.
لكنك غادرت على أي حال.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Why are you so determined?
لماذا انت مصمم هكذا؟
You're not answering your phone.
أنت لا ترد على هاتفك.
It's not a good idea.
هذه ليست فكرة جيدة.
If you say goodbye,
إذا قلت وداعا ،
I don't want to say it again.
لا أريد أن أقولها مرة أخرى.
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
Why do you have to leave?
لماذا عليك المغادرة؟
I can see that
أستطيع أن أرى ذلك
Jiang Nan is sincere to you,
جيانغ نان مخلص لك ،
You like him too.
أنت تحبه أيضًا.
Then why can't two people be together?
إذن لماذا لا يمكن أن يكون شخصان معًا؟
I just want to go back to my normal life,
أريد فقط أن أعود إلى حياتي الطبيعية ،
to be with him,
لتكون معه ،
It's just a contract,
إنه مجرد عقد ،
but it won't end well if you make a fake play.
لكنها لن تنتهي بشكل جيد إذا قدمت مسرحية مزيفة.
When you went back to your hometown with Jiang Nan,
عندما عدت إلى مسقط رأسك مع جيانغ نان ،
did something happen?
هل حدث شئ؟
Nothing happened.
لم يحدث شيء.
It's just that I've figured it out,
لقد فهمت الأمر فقط ،
Keqin,
سيئ،
As my best friend,
كأفضل صديق لي ،
I hope you can support me.
آمل أن تتمكن من دعمني.
Have you figured it out?
هل عرفت ما هو؟
No regrets.
لا ندم.
Okay,
تمام،
No matter what decision you make,
بغض النظر عن القرار الذي تتخذه ،
I'll always be on your side.
سأكون دائما بجانبك.
I don't know what's going on between you two,
لا أعلم ما الذي يحدث بينكما
and Orange won't tell me,
ولن تخبرني "أورانج" ،
Why don't you stop looking for her for a few days.
لماذا لا تتوقف عن البحث عنها لبضعة أيام.
Let her stay at my house for a few days.
دعها تبقى في منزلي لبضعة أيام.
Maybe it will be fine in a few days.
ربما سيكون بخير في غضون أيام قليلة.
Okay,
تمام،
Just do as you say.
فقط افعل كما تقول
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
That's it.
هذا هو.
Same old rules,
نفس القواعد القديمة ،
Why are you frowning?
لماذا انت عابس؟
Come on,
هيا،
Cheers.
هتافات.
In order to celebrate our first collaboration,
للاحتفال بتعاوننا الأول ،
we have achieved a staged victory.
لقد حققنا انتصارا مرحليا.
I didn't expect that the famous Mr. Liang
لم أكن أتوقع أن السيد ليانغ الشهير
only knows this trick.
يعرف هذه الخدعة فقط.
I know what you mean.
أنا أعرف ماذا تقصد.
But we can't rush it.
لكن لا يمكننا التسرع في ذلك.
As you said,
كما قلت،
hit a snake and hit seven inches.
ضرب ثعبان وضرب سبع بوصات.
If we hurt Jiang Nan,
إذا آذينا جيانغ نان ،
we have to hurt his weakness.
علينا أن نؤذي ضعفه.
I think you're right.
أعتقد أنك على حق.
What is Jiang Nan's weakness?
ما هو ضعف جيانغ نان؟
It's his mother.
إنها والدته.
Of course,
بالطبع،
now we have a lot of oranges,
الآن لدينا الكثير من البرتقال ،
Mr. Liang,
السيد ليانغ ،
if you tell me the truth,
إذا قلت لي الحقيقة ،
don't touch many oranges
لا تلمس الكثير من البرتقال
in front of her.
أمامها.
We are enemies.
نحن أعداء.
I didn't expect that Mr. Zhan
لم أكن أتوقع أن السيد زان
is such a lover.
مثل هذا العاشق.
Just do as we said before,
افعل كما قلنا من قبل ،
get what you want.
احصل على ما تريد.
I want my Gu Jiayi,
أريد Gu Jiayi الخاص بي ،
the many oranges I have for you,
الكثير من البرتقال الذي لدي من أجلك ،
Not interested.
غير مهتم.
Are you going to hide from him for the rest of your life?
هل ستختبئين منه لبقية حياتك؟
I don't know
لا أعرف
how long I can hide.
كم من الوقت يمكنني الاختباء.
Okay,
تمام،
I'll go to work now.
سأذهب إلى العمل الآن.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Keqin,
سيئ،
how is Chengcheng?
كيف هي Chengcheng؟
She eats well and sleeps well.
تأكل جيدا وتنام جيدا.
I just don't want to see you.
أنا فقط لا أريد أن أراك.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
You two should know better than I do.
أنتما الاثنان يجب أن تعرفا أفضل مني.
Me,
أنا،
You can't get anything from me.
لا يمكنك الحصول على أي شيء مني.
Jiang Nan,
جيانغ نان ،
friends and wives can't be bullied.
لا يمكن التنمر على الأصدقاء والزوجات.
Keqin has me.
Keqin لديه لي.
Zhu Xiaopang,
تشو شياوبانج
who is your wife?
من هي زوجتك
Well,
نحن سوف،
That's what I meant.
هذا هو ما عنيته.
Jiang Nan understands me.
جيانغ نان يفهمني.
What are you thinking?
بماذا تفكر؟
I'm here to see Chubby
أنا هنا لأرى تشابي
from Chengcheng,
من Chengcheng ،
Are you here to pick me up?
هل انت هنا لاصطحابي؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I'm going to be late.
سوف أتأخر.
Let's go now.
لنذهب الان.
I'm leaving now.
انا راحل الان.
Why are you acting weird today?
لماذا تتصرف بغرابة اليوم؟
I really don't want to be forced by
أنا حقًا لا أريد أن أجبرني
Jiang Nan. Go! Go! Go!
جيانغ نان.  يذهب!  يذهب!  يذهب!
He recovered well after the surgery.
تعافى بشكل جيد بعد الجراحة.
That's good.
هذا جيد.
Happy birthday to you!
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
Hurry up!
عجلوا!
The birthday party is about to begin.
حفلة عيد الميلاد على وشك أن تبدأ.
You said I
قلت أنا
… You forgot to bring the gift.
... نسيت إحضار الهدية.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Happy birthday to you!
عيد ميلاد سعيد!
-Happy birthday! -Happy birthday!
-عيد مولد سعيد!  -عيد مولد سعيد!
Okay. Take a picture.
تمام.  التقط صوره.
Three, two, one.
ثلاثة اثنان واحد.
Stop,
قف،
Chengcheng,
تشنغتشنغ ،
come and take a photo.
تعال والتقط صورة.
Come here! Come here!
تعال الى هنا!  تعال الى هنا!
We're taking pictures.
نحن نلتقط الصور.
-Come on. -It's good. This way. Three,
-هيا.  -إنه جيد.  من هنا.  ثلاثة،
two,
اثنين،
one.
واحد.
Eggplant!
الباذنجان!
I'm sorry that
أنا آسف أن
Sister Doudou is late for something.
الأخت دودو تأخرت عن شيء ما.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
And you're mad at me.
وأنت غاضب مني.
He got up early today,
استيقظ مبكرا اليوم ،
waiting for you and Jiang Nan.
في انتظاركم أنت وجيانغ نان.
Now you two are his best friends.
الآن أنتما الاثنان أعز أصدقائه.
My good friend,
صديقي الجيد،
what gift did I bring you?
ما الهدية التي قدمتها لك؟
Why are they dog food and dog toys?
لماذا هم طعام كلاب ولعب كلاب؟
I don't have a dog at home.
ليس لدي كلب في المنزل.
You'll have it soon.
ستحصل عليه قريبًا.
Chengcheng,
تشنغتشنغ ،
have some of this.
بعض من هذا.
Doudou,
بلانكي
Brother Jiang Nan,
الأخ جيانغ نان ،
Happy birthday!
عيد مولد سعيد!
Thank you, Jiang Nan.
شكرا لك جيانغ نان.
Do you like it?
هل أحببت ذلك؟
Yes,
نعم،
by the way,
على فكرة،
Jiang Nan,
جيانغ نان ،
you came at the right time.
أتيت في الوقت المناسب.
Chengcheng just left.
تشنغتشنغ غادر للتو.
Chengcheng came just now.
جاء Chengcheng للتو.
She went that way.
ذهبت بهذه الطريقة.
Thank you, young man.
شكرا لك أيها الشاب.
Many oranges.
كثير من البرتقال.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Okay, okay.
حسنا حسنا.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Why are you running in such a hurry?
لماذا تجري بهذه السرعة؟
Let's go!
لنذهب!
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Why are you hiding from Jiang Nan?
لماذا تختبئ من جيانغ نان؟
Did he
هل هو
find out that you're sick,
اكتشف أنك مريض ،
No.
رقم.
Don't ask.
لا تسأل.
If you want to cry,
إذا كنت تريد البكاء ،
I can lend you my shoulder.
يمكنني أن أقدم لك كتفي.
I'm sorry
أنا آسف
to drag you into this again.
لسحبك إلى هذا مرة أخرى.
I'm sorry,
أنا آسف،
but I can be your shield.
لكن يمكنني أن أكون درعك.
Jiang Nan will be pissed off again.
سوف يكون جيانغ نان غاضبًا مرة أخرى.
Why not?
لما لا؟
What happened
ماذا حدث
between you and Jiang Nan?
بينك وبين جيانغ نان؟
That day at Jiangnan's hometown,
في ذلك اليوم في مسقط رأس جيانغنان ،
you were like possessed,
كنت ممسوسًا
It's nothing like Zhan Zhilin I knew before,
لا شيء مثل Zhan Zhilin الذي كنت أعرفه من قبل ،
unlike me,
خلافا لي،
That's the real me.
هذا هو حقيقتي.
How much do you know about me?
كم تعرف عني؟
Maybe I don't know you that well.
ربما لا أعرفك جيدًا.
But I know,
لكني اعرف،
what you did that day was impulsive.
ما فعلته في ذلك اليوم كان مندفعًا.
I don't want to talk about this anymore.
لا أريد أن أتحدث عن هذا بعد الآن.
That day at Jiangnan's hometown,
في ذلك اليوم في مسقط رأس جيانغنان ،
you were like possessed,
كنت ممسوسًا
It's nothing like Zhan Zhilin I knew before.
لا شيء مثل Zhan Zhilin الذي كنت أعرفه من قبل.
My dad gave you money.
أعطاك والدي المال.
I saw it.
رأيته.
Jiang Nan,
جيانغ نان ،
did you already know all this?
هل تعلم بالفعل كل هذا؟
Then why didn't you tell me?
ثم لماذا لم تخبرني؟
If you tell me,
إذا أخبرتني ،
I can still save my mom.
لا يزال بإمكاني إنقاذ أمي.
My mom wouldn't have died.
أمي ما كانت لتموت.
The grudges of the previous generation,
ضغائن الجيل السابق ،
have nothing to do with us.
لا علاقة لنا به.
Jiang Nan,
جيانغ نان ،
are you talking in human language?
هل تتحدث بلغة بشرية
You're clearly protecting your mom.
من الواضح أنك تحمي والدتك.
No wonder
لا عجب
you want to break up the group?
تريد تفريق المجموعة؟
Because you don't have the face to see me.
لأنك لا تملك الوجه لرؤيتي.
Are you done scolding me?
هل انتهيت من تأنيبي؟
I'll leave if you're done scolding me.
سأرحل إذا انتهيت من توبيخي.
I won't let you and your mom end well.
لن أتركك أنت وأمك تنتهي بشكل جيد.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Where are you now?
اين انت الان؟
Did you tell the truth about the nursing home?
هل قلت الحقيقة عن دار المسنين؟
From what standpoint do you ask this?
من أي وجهة نظر تسأل هذا؟
Why should I answer you?
لماذا يجب علي الرد عليك
Jiang Nan is indiscriminate,
جيانغ نان عشوائي ،
so he came to ask me if I did it?
لذلك جاء ليسألني إذا فعلت ذلك؟
Who else could it be besides you?
من غيرك يمكن أن يكون بجانبك؟
I'm not the only one
انا لست الوحيد
who wants to mess with Jiang Nan.
الذي يريد العبث مع جيانغ نان.
It's Liang Zhe.
إنه ليانغ زهي.
Let me tell you one more thing.
دعني أخبرك بشيء آخر.
Many oranges have moved out of Jiangnan's house.
انتقل العديد من البرتقال من منزل جيانغنان.
So don't waste your energy
لذلك لا تضيعوا طاقتكم
on her.
عليها.
Xiao Mei,
شياو مي
pick up the show for me last time.
التقط العرض لي آخر مرة.
I want Jiang Nan to see the shining me again.
أريد أن يرى جيانغ نان أشعاني مرة أخرى.